Register to the United States. Subversive Activities Control Board records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Individual Case Findings, 1962-1969. (Box 86-88)
  - Docket I-17-63: Mildred McAdory Edelman. Recommended decision, 1963; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-18-63: Irving Potash. Recommended decision, 1963; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-19-63: William Wolf Weinstone. Recommended decision, 1963; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-20-63: Mortimer Daniel Rubin. Report and order of the Board, 1963 (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-21-63: John William Stanford, Jr. Recommended decision, 1963; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-22-63: Benjamin Dobbs. Recommended decision, 1963; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-23-63: William Cottle Taylor. Recommended decision, 1963; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-24-63: Frances Gabow. Recommended decision, 1963; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-25-63: Aaron Libson. Recommended decision, 1963; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-26-63: Lionel Joseph Libson. Recommended decision, 1964; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-27-63: James Joseph Tormey. Recommended decision, 1964; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-28-64: Michael Saunders. Recommended decision, 1964; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-29-64: Daniel Lieber Queen. Recommended decision, 1964; report and order of the Board (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-30-64: Ralph William Taylor. Report and order of the Board, 1964 (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-31-64: Betty Mae Smith. Report and order of the Board, 1964 (Folder 87)
  - Docket I-32-64: Marvin Joel Markman. Recommended decision, 1964; report and order of the Board, 1965 (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-33-64: Meyer Jacob Stein. Recommended decision, 1964; report and order of the Board, 1965 (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-34-64: Norman Haaland. Report and order of the Board, undated (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-35-64: Benjamin Gerald Jacobson. Report and order of the Board, 1964 (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-36-64: Milford Adolf Sutherland. Report and order of the Board, 1964 (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-37-64: Donald Andrew Hamerquist. Report and order of the Board, 1964 (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-38-65: Hyman Lumer. Recommended decision, 1965; report and order of the Board (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-39-65: Elmer Charles Kistler. Report and order of the Board, 1965 (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-40-65: Ralph Nelson. Recommended decision, 1965; report and order of the Board (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-41-65: Otis Archer Hood. Recommended decision, 1965; report and order of the Board (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-42-65: Lewis Martin Johnson. Recommended decision, 1965; report and order of the Board (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-43-65: Edward S. Teixeira. Recommended decision, 1965; report and order of the Board (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-44-65: Anne Burlak Timpson. Recommended decision, 1965; report and order of the Board (Folder 88)
  - Dockets I-45-69 and I-46-69: Robert Archuleta and Wayne Dallas Holley. Report and order, 1968 (Folder 88)
  - Dockets I-47-69 and I-48-69: Anna Pastor Laconich and Ruth Beer. Report and order, 1969 (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-49-69: Scarlett Ann Patrick. Report and order, 1969 (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-50-69: Simon Boorda. Report and order, 1968 (Folder 88)
  - Dockets I-52-69 and I-53-69: Clifford Fried and David Utter Mares. Report and order, 1969 (Folder 88)
  - Docket I-54-69: Kenneth William Applehans. Report and order, 1969 (Folder 88)
- Reports, 1951-1973. (Box 89-90)
  Printed annual reports and compiled case decisions of the Board.
  - Annual Reports of the Board, 1st through 22nd, 1951-1973. (Folder 89)
  - Bound volume of Annual Reports, 1st through 15th, 1951-1965. (Folder 89)
  - Reports of the Subversive Activities Control Board, Volumes I-IV and Index-Digest, 1966 (Folder 90)
  - U.S. Congress. House. Committee on Internal Security. Hearings Regarding the Administration of the Subversive Activities Control Act of 1950 and the Federal Civilian Employee Loyalty-Security Program. Part I, 1971 (Folder 90)